<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Evolution of Pyschotherapy</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="go_to_erickson_website">Visit Erickson Website</string>
    <string name="server_error">Server Error</string>
    <string name="loading_info">Loading Info&#8230;</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="empty_schedule_day">Nothing to Display</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_schedule">ScheduleActivity</string>
    <string name="pref_sync">Pref Sync</string>
    <string name="pref_sync_summ">Pref Sync Summ</string>
    <string name="no_info">No Information to Display. Should there be? Let us know on the Feedback page</string>
    <string name="submit_btn">Submit</string>
    <string name="clear_btn">Clear</string>
    <string name="twitter_consumer_key">30QCzhZ13e3U7Ox29pZT7O7XB</string>
    <string name="twitter_consumer_secret">hGUmN8NumH1438rkVrID8vcg3Qh0wUBziuqtjpwIsF9Z47bcT4</string>
    <string name="player_error">Error initializing Youtube player: %s</string>
    <string name="seek_to">Jump To</string>
    <string name="seek_to_hint">Seconds</string>
    <string name="placeholder_event_name">Placeholder Event Name</string>
    <string name="event_details">Event Details/Description</string>
    <string name="maps">Maps</string>
    <string name="speakers">Speakers</string>
    <string name="all_speakers">All Speakers</string>
    <string name="schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="Syllabus">Syllabus</string>
    <string name="twitter">Twitter</string>
    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="syllabus">Syllabus</string>
    <string name="parking_info">Parking Info</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="filter">Filter</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="no_talks_favorited">No Talks Favorited on this day</string>
    <string name="add_to_favorites">Add To Favorites</string>
    <string name="remove_from_favorites">Remove From Favorites</string>
    <string name="go_to_map">Go To Map</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="placeholder_text">Placeholder Text</string>
    <string name="placeholder_bio_text">Placeholder Speaker Bio</string>
    <string name="speaker_bio">Bio</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="send_us_feedback">Send us Feedback</string>
    <string name="panels">Panels</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!--String Bios for each speaker, temporary solution, this should be externalized for future releases***-->
    <string name="michael_yapko_bio">Michael D. Yapko, Ph.D. (professional psychology, clinical specialization), is internationally recognized for his innovative work in applied clinical hypnosis, developing brief psychotherapies, and the strategic treatment of depression. He has been invited to present his work in more than 30 countries across six continents. He is the author of 15 books, including his most recent, The Discriminating Therapist. He is a recipient of numerous awards for his many contributions to the field, including the Milton H. Erickson Foundation Lifetime Achievement Award. More information is available on Dr. Yapko’s website, www.yapko.com.</string>
    <string name="daniel_amen_bio">Daniel Amen, MD is a double board-certified psychiatrist, multiple NY Times bestselling author, founder of Amen Clinics and brain imaging pioneer. He has written and hosted 11 public television specials about the brain. Discover Magazine named his brain imaging research as one of the top 100 stories in all of Science for 2015.</string>
    <string name="steve_frankel_bio">A practicing licensing board defense attorney and clinical/forensic psychologist, Steven Frankel is a PhD of Indiana University, interned at Columbia University, and served as a full-time clinical psychology faculty member at USC for 11 years, 5 years as Director of Clinical Training. A Clinical Professor at USC and a past Adjunct faculty member at Loyola (L.A.) and Golden Gate law schools, Steve has received awards for teaching excellence in law/psychology interfaces and in trauma assessment and treatment, which has been his specialty since 1980. He has authored the chapter on Risk Management for trauma clinicians in APA’S forthcoming Handbook of Trauma. His Practice-Legacy Programs work was created to protect clinicians, their families and patients/clients from failures to prepare for unanticipated death or disability.</string>
    <string name="david_whyte_bio">DAVID WHYTE Poet, Author, Lecturer David Whyte grew up with a strong, imaginative influence from his Irish mother among the hills and valleys of his father’s Yorkshire. He now makes his home in the Pacific Northwest of the United States.
                                    The author of eight books of poetry and four books of prose, David Whyte holds a degree in Marine Zoology and has traveled extensively, including living and working as a naturalist guide in the Galapagos Islands and leading anthropological and natural history expeditions in the Andes, Amazon and Himalaya. He brings this wealth of experience to his poetry, lectures and workshops.
                                    His life as a poet has created a readership and listenership in three normally mutually exclusive areas: the literate world of readings that most poets inhabit, the psychological and theological worlds of philosophical enquiry and the world of vocation, work and organizational leadership.
                                    An Associate Fellow at Said Business School at the University of Oxford, he is one of the few poets to take his perspectives on creativity into the field of organizational development, where he works with many Europen, American and international companies. In spring 2008 he was awarded an honorary doctorate from Neumann College, Pennsylvania.
                                    In organizational settings, using poetry and thoughtful commentary, he illustrates how we can foster qualities of courage and engagement; qualities needed if we are to respond to today’s call for increased creativity and adaptability in the workplace. He brings a unique and important contribution to our understanding of the nature of individual and organizational change, particularly through his unique perspectives on Conversational Leadership.</string>
    <string name="robert_sapolsky_bio">Robert Sapolsky, Ph.D in Neuroendocrinology\nAs a boy in New York City, Robert M. Sapolsky dreamed of living inside the African dioramas in the Museum of Natural History. By the age of twenty-one, he made it to Africa and joined a troop of baboons. Although the life of a naturalist appealed to him because it was a chance to “get the hell out of Brooklyn,” he never really left people behind.\n
                                    In fact, he chose to live with the baboons because they are perfect for learning about stress and stress-related diseases in humans. Like their human cousins, baboons live in large, complex social groups and have lots of time, Dr. Sapolsky writes, “to devote to being rotten to each other.” Just like stressed-out people, stressed-out baboons have high blood pressure, high cholesterol, and hardened arteries. And just like people, baboons are good material for stories. His gift for storytelling led The New York Times to suggest, “If you crossed Jane Goodall with a borscht-belt comedian, she might have written a book like A Primate’s Memoir,” Dr. Sapolsky’s account of his early years as a field biologist.\n
                                    The uniqueness of Sapolsky’s perspective on the human condition comes from the ease with which he combines his insights from the field with his findings as a neuroscientist. For more than thirty years Sapolsky has divided his time between field work with baboons and highly technical neurological research in the laboratory. As a result, he can effortlessly move from a discussion of pecking orders in primate societies (human and baboon) to an explanation of how neurotransmitters work during stress—and get laughs doing it. The problem for people, as Dr. Sapolsky explains in his book Why Zebras Don’t Get Ulcers, is that our bodies’ stress response evolved to help us get out of short-term physical emergencies—if a lion is chasing you, you run. But such reactions, he points out, compromise long-term physical health in favor of immediate self-preservation. Unfortunately, when confronted with purely psychological stressors, such as troubleshooting the fax machine, modern humans turn on the same stress response. “If you turn it on for too long,” notes Sapolsky, “you get sick.” Sapolsky regards this sobering news with characteristic good humor, finding hope in “our own capacity to prevent some of these problems…in the small steps with which we live our everyday lives.”\n
                                    The humor and humanity he brings to sometimes-sobering subject matter make Dr. Sapolsky a fascinating speaker. He lectures widely on topics as diverse as stress and stress-related diseases, baboons, the biology of our individuality, the biology of religious belief, the biology of memory, schizophrenia, depression, aggression, and Alzheimer’s disease.\n
                                    Dr. Sapolsky is a MacArthur “Genius” Fellow, a professor of biology and neurology at Stanford University, and a research associate with the Institute of Primate Research at the National Museum of Kenya. In 2008, National Geographic &amp; PBS aired an hour-long special on stress featuring Dr. Sapolsky and his research on the subject. In addition to A Primate’s Memoir, which won the 2001 Bay Area Book Reviewers Award in nonfiction, Robert Sapolsky has written three other books, including The Trouble with Testosterone, Why Zebras Don’t Get Ulcers, and Monkeyluv and Other Essays on our Lives as Animals. Dr. Sapolsky was awarded Rockefeller University’s Lewis Thomas Prize for Writing about Science for 2008. His articles have appeared in publications such as Discover and The New Yorker, and he writes a biweekly column for the Wall Street Journal entitled “Mind &amp; Matter.” He is currently working on a book to be titled: Behave: The Biology of Humans at Our Best and Worst (Penguin Press May 2017).</string>
    <string name="derald_wing_bio">Derald Wing Sue, Ph.D in Counselling Psychology, is Professor of Psychology and Education in the Department of Counseling and Clinical Psychology at Teachers College and the School of Social Work, Columbia University. He was the co-founder of the National Multicultural Conference and Summit, co-founder and first President of the Asian American Psychological Association, past presidents of
                                    the Society for the Psychological Study of Culture, Ethnicity and Race, and the Society of Counseling Psychology.  Derald has served as Editor of the Journal for Counseling and Development, Associate Editor of the American Psychologist, Editorial Board Member to The Counseling Psychologist, Asian American Journal of Psychology, Asian Journal of Counselling, and serves on the Council of Elders
                                    for Cultural Diversity and Ethnic Minority Psychology.\n\nDerald is a pioneer in the field of multicultural psychology, microaggression theory, racial dialogues, multicultural counseling and therapy, and the psychology of racism/antiracism.  He is author of four best-selling texts: (1) COUNSELING THE CULTURALLY DIVERSE:  THEORY AND PRACTICE, (2) OVERCOMING OUR RACISM:  THE JOURNEY TO LIBERATION,
                                    (3) MICROAGGRESSIONS IN EVERYDAY LIFE:  RACE, GENDER AND SEXUAL ORIENTATION, and (4) RACE TALK  AND THE CONSPIRACY OF SILENCE: UNDERSTANDING AND FACILITATING DIFFICULT DIALOGUES ON RACE. As evidence of Dr. Sue’s stature in the field, two studies of multicultural publications and scholars concluded, Impressively, Derald Wing Sue is without doubt the most influential multicultural scholar in the United States today.</string>
    <string name="bill_o_hanlon_bio">Bill O’Hanlon, MS (Family Studies), LMFT, has authored or co-authored 35 books. His books have been translated into 17 languages. He has appeared on Oprah (with his book Do One Thing Different), The Today Show, and a variety of other television and radio programs. Since 1977, Bill has given over 3500 talks around the world. Bill is a Licensed Mental Health Professional, Certified Professional Counselor,
                                    and a Licensed Marriage and Family Therapist. Bill is clinical member of AAMFT (and winner of the 2003 New Mexico AMFT Distinguished Service Award), certified by the National Board of Certified Clinical Hypnotherapists and a Fellow and a Board Member of the American Psychotherapy Association.</string>
    <string name="scott_miller_bio">Scott D. Miller, Ph.D. received his Doctor of Philosophy degree in APA-approved Counseling Psychology in the Department of Educational Psychology at the University of Utah. He is the founder of the International Center for Clinical Excellence an international consortium of clinicians, researchers, and educators dedicated to promoting excellence in behavioral health services. Dr. Miller conducts workshops
                                    and training in the United States and abroad, helping hundreds of agencies and organizations, both public and private, to achieve superior results. His humorous and engaging presentation style and command of the research literature consistently inspires practitioners, administrators, and policy makers to make effective changes in service delivery.</string>
</resources>
